Guide to the Carl B. Hess Papers MC.229
New York University Archives
- Series III. Professional, 1942-2011; 12 Linear Feet in 27 manuscript boxes and 2 card boxes.
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Whitehead, John, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Wilkinson, Alan, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Williams, John, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor Interview -- Wriston, Walter, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor -- Notes, Letters, Draft Comments, Research, 1985-1993 (Box 45, Folder 8-12)
  - American European Associates -- Profit with Honor -- Book, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
  - American European Associates -- Travel Expense Charts, Schedules, Research, 1969-1991 (Box 46, Folder 3-12, Box 47, Folder 1-24, Box 48, Folder 1-13)
  - Hess Press -- Planning Documentation, Letters, 1996-1997 (Box 48, Folder 14-16)